[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the winter of 1998-1999 this U.S. state broke the record of Mt. Ranier from 1971-1972 for the largest amount of cumulative snowfall in history.", "correct_answer": "Washington", "incorrect_answers": ["Maine", "Montana", "Alaska"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Lex Luthors girlfriend in the film Superman Returns?", "correct_answer": "Kitty", "incorrect_answers": ["Cookie", "Mary", "Amila"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long do you need to boil an egg for it to be considered hard boiled?", "correct_answer": "10 -11 minutes", "incorrect_answers": ["5 - 6 minutes", "30 minutes", "1 hour"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These worms are not in fact worms, but bivalves. They enter wood as larvae, where they remain and grow, burrowing through the wood.", "correct_answer": "Shipworms", "incorrect_answers": ["Sea Mice", "Ribbon Worms", "Lugworms"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Youre gonna need a bigger boat is a quote from this 1975 movie.", "correct_answer": "Jaws", "incorrect_answers": ["Free Willy", "Moby Dick", "Titanic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Trepanation is a term that denotes making a hole in this part of the body.", "correct_answer": "Skull", "incorrect_answers": ["Hand", "Eyelid", "Foot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this fine movie Dustin Hoffman plays a mathematician who gets tired of being picked on.", "correct_answer": "Straw Dogs", "incorrect_answers": ["Sunday Father", "The Point", "Sphere"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these US Presidents had the shortest tenure?", "correct_answer": "James A. Garfield", "incorrect_answers": ["James Carter", "James Madison", "James K. Polk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Charlie Chaplins first feature-length film, also directed by him?", "correct_answer": "The Kid", "incorrect_answers": ["Pay Day", "A Days Pleasure", "The Gold Rush"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "HCl has pH close to which one of these?", "correct_answer": "2", "incorrect_answers": ["4", "14", "7"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Italian car make, founded in 1963, has a bull on its emblem.", "correct_answer": "Lamborghini", "incorrect_answers": ["Ferrari", "Maserati", "Alfa Romeo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these actors did not star in Martin Scorseses 1991 thriller Cape Fear?", "correct_answer": "Daniel Day-Lewis", "incorrect_answers": ["Juliette Lewis", "Nick Nolte", "Jessica Lange"]}]